Guide to the Edwin and Terry Murray Comic Book Collection
Edwin and Terry Murray Comic Book Collection
- Marvel Comics
  - Contents of Box 208: (Box 208)
    - Title from indicia: X-Men: Books of Askani, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: X-Men Chronicles, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: X-Men '95, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: X-Men Omega, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: X-Men Prime, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: X-Men 2099, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: X-Men 2099 Special, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: X-Men Unlimited, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: X-Nation 2099, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: X-Universe, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Zorro, Issues from: 1990s
  - Contents of Box 209: (Box 209)
    - Title from indicia: The Amazing Spider-Man, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Amazing Spider-Man Annual, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Amazing Spider-Man '97, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Daily Bugle, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Deadly Foes of Spider-Man, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Rise of Apocalypse, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Osborne Journals, Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: Spider-Man: The Osborn Journal
    - Title from indicia: The Punisher, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Punisher Annual, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Punisher Armory, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Punisher the Prize, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Punisher 2099, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Punisher War Journal, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Punisher: War Zone, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Sensational Spider-Man, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Spectacular Spider-Man, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Spider-Man, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Spider-Man/Badrock, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Spider-Man: Dead Man's Hand, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Spider-Man: Hobgoblin Lives, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Spider-Man Saga, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Spider-Man Team-Up, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Spider-Man Unlimited, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Untold Tales of Spider-Man, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Venom: License to Kill, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Venom: On Trial, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Venom: Seed of Darkness, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Venom: Tooth and Claw, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Web of Spider-Man, Issues from: 1990s
  - Contents of Box 210: (Box 210)
    - Title from indicia: Abomination, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Adventures of Captain America, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Alpha Flight, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Avengers, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Avengers Spotlight, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Avengers West Coast, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Brute Force, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Cage, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Captain America, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Captain America Annual, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Cloak and Dagger, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Code of Honor, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Conan, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Conan the Barbarian, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Cyblade/Ghost Rider, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Elektra, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Ghost Rider, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Ghost Rider/Blaze: Spirits of Vengeance, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Hercules: Heart of Chaos, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Hero, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Heroes for Hire, Issues from: 1990s
  - Contents of Box 211: (Box 211)
    - Title from indicia: Damage Control, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Daredevil, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Daredevil Annual, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Daredevil/Deadpool '97, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Daredevil/Shi, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Darkhawk, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Darkhold: Pages From the Book of Sins, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Darkman, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Daydreamers, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Deadpool, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Deathlok, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Destroyer, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Devil Dinosaur Spring Fling, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Doctor Strange, Sorcerer Supreme, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Domino, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Doom 2099, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Fantastic Four, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Fantastic Four Annual, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Foolkiller, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: G.I. Joe A Real American Hero, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Gladiator/Supreme, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Guardians of the Galaxy, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Guardians of the Galaxy Annual, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Journey Into Mystery, Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: Journey Into Mystery Featuring the Lost Gods
    - Title from indicia: Ka-Zar, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Ka-Zar: Sibling Rivalry, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Knights of Pendragon, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Ravage 2099, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Shi/Daredevil, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: 2099: World of Tomorrow, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Valkyrie, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Zorro, Issues from: 1990s
  - Contents of Box 212: (Box 212)
    - Title from indicia: The Incredible Hulk, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Infinity Gauntlet, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Invaders, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Iron Man, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Iron Man Annual, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Marc Spector: Moon Knight, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Marvel Comics Presents, Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: Marvel Comics Presents Before Wolverine There Was Weapon X
      - Cover Title: Marvel Comics Presents Ghost Rider and Cable/Wolverine
      - Cover Title: Marvel Comics Presents Weapon X
      - Cover Title: Marvel Comics Presents Wolverine
      - Cover Title: Marvel Comics Presents Wolverine and Ghost Rider
      - Cover Title: Marvel Comics Presents Wolverine and the Incredible Hulk
      - Cover Title: Marvel Comics Presents Wolverine/Ghost Rider and Typhoid Mary
      - Cover Title: Marvel Comics Presents Wolverine vs. the Incredible Hulk
    - Title from indicia: Marvel Fanfare, Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: Marvel Fanfare
      - Cover Title: Marvel Fanfare: When Knights Were Bold
      - Cover Title: Marvel Fanfare: When Strikes the Assassin
    - Title from indicia: Marvel Holiday Special, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Marvel: Shadows and Light, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Marvel Super-Heroes, Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: Marvel Super-Heroes Spring Special
      - Cover Title: Marvel Super-Heroes Summer Special
      - Cover Title: Marvel Super-Heroes Winter Special
    - Title from indicia: Marvel Team-Up, Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: Marvel Team-Up Starring Spider-Man and Generation X
    - Title from indicia: Marvel Valentine Special, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Master of Kung-Fu: Bleeding Black, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Mighty Thor, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Mighty Thor Annual, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The New Warriors, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The New Warriors Annual, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: NFL Super Pro, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Power Pack, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Prophet/Cable, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Psylocke & Archangel Crimson Dawn, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Thor, Issues from: 1990s
  - Contents of Box 213: (Box 213)
    - Title from indicia: The 'Nam, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Namor, The Sub-Mariner, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Nick Fury, Agent of S.H.I.E.L.D., Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Nightcat, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Nightstalkers, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Nomad, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Quasar, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Robocop, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Secret Defenders, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Sensational She-Hulk, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Sergio Aragonés Groo the Wanderer, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: She-Hulk, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Silver Sable and the Wild Pack, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Silver Surfer, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Silver Surfer Annual, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Silver Surfer '97, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Silver Surfer/Superman, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Silver Surfer/Weapon Zero, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Sleepwalker, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Stalkers, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Starlord, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Tales of Age of Apocalypse, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Tales of the Marvels: Inner Demons, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Thanos Quest, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Thunderbolts, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Thunderbolts '97, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Weapon Zero/Silver Surfer, Issues from: 1990s
  - Contents of Box 214: (Box 214)
    - Title from indicia: Beast, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Cable, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Excalibur, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Excalibur: The Possession, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Generation X, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Imperial Guard, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Magneto, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Mystique & Sabretooth, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The New Mutants, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The New Mutants Annual, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Onslaught: Epilogue, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Professor Xavier and the X-Men, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Strong Guy Reborn, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Uncanny X-Men, Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: The Uncanny X-Men
      - Cover Title: X-Men
    - Title from indicia: X-Factor, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: X-Force, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: X-Force/Cable '97, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: X-Man, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: X-Men, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: X-Men Annual, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: X-Men: Lost Tales, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: X-Men '97, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: X-Men 1, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: X-Men Unlimited, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: XSE, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Youngblood/X-Force, Issues from: 1990s
  - Contents of Box 215: (Box 215)
    - Title from indicia: Maverick, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Star Trek: Deep Space Nine, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Star Trek: Early Voyages, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Star Trek: Operation Assimilation, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Star Trek: Starfleet Academy, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Star Trek Unlimited, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Star Trek: Voyager, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Terror Inc., Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: Terror Inc. and Wolverine
    - Title from indicia: Thunderstrike, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Transformers, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Ultragirl, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Uncanny Origins, Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: Uncanny Origins Featuring the Beast
      - Cover Title: Uncanny Origins Featuring Daredevil
      - Cover Title: Uncanny Origins Featuring Doctor Strange, Sorcerer Supreme
      - Cover Title: Uncanny Origins Featuring Felicia Hardy: The Black Cat
      - Cover Title: Uncanny Origins Featuring the Incredible Hulk
      - Cover Title: Uncanny Origins Featuring Nightcrawler
      - Cover Title: Uncanny Origins Featuring Storm
    - Title from indicia: The Untold Legend of Captain Marvel, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: War Machine, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: What If...?, Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: What If...The All-New All-Different X-Men had Never Existed?
      - Cover Title: What If...The Amazing Spider-Man had Married the Black Cat?
      - Cover Title: What If...The Amazing Spider-Man had not Married Mary Jane?
      - Cover Title: What If...Archangel Fell From Grace?
      - Cover Title: What If...Barbara Ketch had Become Ghost Rider?
      - Cover Title: What If...Cable had Destroyed the X-Men?
      - Cover Title: What If...Captain America had Led an Army of Super Soldiers in World War II?
      - Cover Title: What If...Daredevil had Saved Nuke?
      - Cover Title: What If...The Fantastic Four Battled Doctor Doom Before They Got Their Powers?
      - Cover Title: What If...The Fantastic Four's Second Child Had Lived?
      - Cover Title: What If...Iron Man Sold Out?
      - Cover Title: What If...Magneto Took Over the USA?
      - Cover Title: What If...Marvel Super-Heroes had Lost Atlantis Attacks?
      - Cover Title: What If...Namor had Joined the Fantastic Four?
      - Cover Title: What If...The Punisher Became Captain America?
      - Cover Title: What If...The Punisher had Killed Daredevil?
      - Cover Title: What If...The Silver Surfer had not Escaped Earth?
      - Cover Title: What If...The Silver Surfer Possessed the Infinity Gauntlet?
      - Cover Title: What If...Spider-Man had Kept his Cosmic Powers?
      - Cover Title: What If...Spider-Man's Parents Destroyed his Family?
      - Cover Title: What If...? Starring Black Knight
      - Cover Title: What If...? Starring Gambit
      - Cover Title: What If...? Starring The Juggernaut
      - Cover Title: What If...? Starring Quick Silver
      - Cover Title: What If...? Starring Rogue
      - Cover Title: What If...? Starring Spider-Man
      - Cover Title: What If...? Starring Wolverine
      - Cover Title: What If...War Machine had not Destroyed the Living Laser?
      - Cover Title: What If...Wolverine Battled Weapon X?
      - Cover Title: What If...Wolverine had Married Mariko?
      - Cover Title: What If...Wolverine was Lord of the Vampires?
    - Title from indicia: Wolverine, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Wolverine Annual 2, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Wolverine Encyclopedia, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Wonder Man, Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: Wonder Man
      - Cover Title: Hidden Depths: Wonder Man
  - Contents of Box 216: (Box 216)
    - Title from indicia: The Amazing Spider-Man, Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: The Amazing Spider-Man
      - Cover Title: The Amazing Spider-Man: Giant Sized 30th Anniversary of the Amazing Spider-Man #1
    - Title from indicia: The Amazing Spider-Man Annual, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Amazing Spider-Man: Chaos in Calgary, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Amazing Spider-Man: Double Trouble, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Amazing Spider-Man: Hit and Run, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Amazing Spider-Man: Skating on Thin Ice, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Amazing Spider-Man Soul of the Hunter, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Shroud, Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: The Scorpion vs. The Shroud
    - Title from indicia: Scarlet Witch, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Secret Defenders, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Silver Sable and the Wild Pack, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Silver Surfer, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Silver Surfer/Warlock: The Resurrections, Issues from:1990s
    - Title from indicia: Sleepwalker, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Sleepwalker Holiday Special, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Solo, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Spectacular Spider-Man, Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: The Spectacular Spider-Man
      - Cover Title: X-Men in the Spectacular Spider-Man
      - Cover Title: The Spectacular Spider-Man: Pursuit
      - Cover Title: The Spectacular Spider-Man: Giant Sized 200th Issue
    - Title from indicia: The Spectacular Spider-Man Annual, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Spider-Man, Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: Spider-Man
      - Cover Title: The Punisher Stalks Spider-Man
      - Cover Title: Spider-Man: Pursuit
    - Title from indicia: Spider-Man: The Arachnis Project, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Spider-Man: The Mutant Agenda, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Spider-Man, Punisher, Sabretooth: Designer Genes, Issues from:1990s
    - Title from indicia: Spider-Man 2099, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Spider-Man 2099 Annual, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Spider-Man Unlimited, Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: Spider-Man Unlimited
      - Cover Title: Spider-Man Unlimited: Maximun Carnage Begins Here!
    - Title from indicia: Spider-Man: Web of Doom, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Spider-Man and X-Factor: Shadowgames, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Venom: Lethal Protector, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Venom: The Mace, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Venom: Nights of Vengeance, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Venom: Enemy Within, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Web of Spider-Man, Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: Web of Spider-Man
      - Cover Title: Web of Spider-Man: Maximun Carnage
  - Contents of Box 217: (Box 217)
    - Title from indicia: Adventures of Cyclops and Phoenix, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Cable, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Deadpool, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Doom 2099, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Excalibur, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The New Warriors, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Official Marvel Index to the X-Men, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Ravage 2099, Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: Ravage 2099
      - Cover Title: All of 2099 vs. Ravage
    - Title from indicia: Styfe's Strike File, Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: Styfe's Strike File
      - Cover Title: Styfe's Strike File: An X-Cutioner's Song Addendum
    - Title from indicia: 2099 Unlimited, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Uncanny X-Men, Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: Uncanny X-Men
      - Cover Title: Uncanny X-Men: X-Cutioner's Song
    - Title from indicia: Uncanny X-Men Annual, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: X-Factor, Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: X-Factor
      - Cover Title: X-Factor: X-Cutioner's Song
    - Title from indicia: X-Factor Annual, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: X-Force, Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: X-Force
      - Cover Title: X-Force: X-Cutioner's Song
    - Title from indicia: X-Men, Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: X-Men
      - Cover Title: X-Men: X-Cutioner's Song
    - Title from indicia: X-Men Adventures, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: X-Men 2099, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: X-Men Unlimited, Issues from: 1990s
  - Contents of Box 218: (Box 218)
    - Title from indicia: The Infinity Crusade, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Infinity War, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Iron Man, Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: Iron Man
      - Cover Title: Iron Man 48 Page Anniversary Special
      - Cover Title: Iron Man 30th Anniversary Special
    - Title from indicia: Iron Manual, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Justice: Four Balance, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Knights of Pendragon, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Marc Spector: Moon Knight, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Marvel Comics Presents, Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: Marvel Comics Presents Clan Destine Vengeance Shang Chi New Warriors
      - Cover Title: Marvel Comics Presents Ghost Rider/Wolverine
      - Cover Title: Marvel Comics Presents Ghost Rider and Cage/Wolverine
      - Cover Title: Marvel Comics Presents Ghost Rider and Cage/Wolverine and Venom
      - Cover Title: Marvel Comics Presents Ghost Rider and Cloak and Dagger/Wolverine and Venom
      - Cover Title: Marvel Comics Presents Ghost Rider and Iron Fist/Wolverine
      - Cover Title: Marvel Comics Presents Ghost Rider and Iron Fist/Wolverine and Giant Man
      - Cover Title: Marvel Comics Presents Ghost Rider and Iron Fist/Wolverine and Typhoid Mary
      - Cover Title: Marvel Comics Presents Ghost Rider and Typhoid Mary/Wolverine
      - Cover Title: Marvel Comics Presents Hawkeye Nick Fury Vengeance New Warriors
      - Cover Title: Marvel Comics Presents Mace New Warriors Vengeance Hawkeye
      - Cover Title: Marvel Comics Presents New Warriors/Vengeance Mace New Warriors Tigra
      - Cover Title: Marvel Comics Presents New Warriors Mace Vengeance Hawkeye
      - Cover Title: Marvel Comics Presents Tigra New Warriors Vengeance Mace
      - Cover Title: Marvel Comics Presents Wolverine Daredevil Vengenace Typhoid
      - Cover Title: Marvel Comics Presents Wolverine War Machine Moon Knight Vengeance
    - Title from indicia: Marvel Double Feature...The Avengers/Giant Man, Issues from:1990s
    - Title from indicia: Marvel Double Feature...Thunderstrike/Code Blue, Issues from:1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Marvel Masterpieces Collection, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Marvel Masterpieces 2 Collection, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Marvel Holiday Special, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Marvels, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Marvel Super-Heroes, Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: The All-Iron Man Issue of Marvel Super-Heroes 80 Page Spring Special
      - Cover Title: Falcon Dr. Strange Iron Man Marvel Super-Heroes 80 Page Winter Special
    - Title from indicia: Midnight Sons Unlimited, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Mighty Thor, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Mighty Thor Annual, Issues from: 1990s